csx.com 2006-06-15

# Welcome to CSX.com - Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

CSX Corporation is committed to Internet privacy and information security. In general, you can visit us on the World Wide Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. Our web servers collect the IP addresses, not the e-mail addresses, of visitors. This information is aggregated to measure the number of visits, average time spent on the site, pages viewed, etc. We use this information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content of our site. 

There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name, e-mail address, and mailing address. Usually, we use the information we collect to respond to your inquiry, process an order, or allow you to access specific account information. We will not share your information with anyone other than CSX Corp.'s subsidiaries or affiliates. 

If you register with one of CSX Corp.'s subsidiaries or affiliates on-line, they may use this information to provide you with customized information about offerings that support your specific business needs. A technology called "cookies" may be used to provide you with such customized information. A cookie is a tiny element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer's hard drive so we can recognize you when you return. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. 

At times we conduct on-line surveys to better understand our visitors' needs. When we conduct a survey, we will let you know how we will use your information at the time we collect it.

We do not send unsolicited e-mail. After you provide us with personal information, you may receive Service Bulletins, electronic newsletters, or other materials of interest to you via e-mail from CSX Corp. or its subsidiaries or affiliates. 

You may easily unsubscribe to future e-mailings by using any of the following methods:

  * Via our web site, by visiting the Unsubscribe Page.

CSX Corp.'s web site may contain links to other sites, such as government organizations and affiliates. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for other sites' content or privacy practices.

CSX Corp. has certified to the United States Department of Commerce that, for personal data transferred from the European Union to the United States, it will apply the Safe Harbor Principles. The Safe Harbor Principles ensure that: 

  * Notice is given about the purposes for which information is collected;
  * Choice is offered to individuals to decide whether personal information should be disclosed either to a third party or for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected;
  * Onward transfer occurs only after CSX Corp. has determined that a third party receiving the information provides at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the Safe Harbor Principles;
  * Security is provided to protect personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction;
  * Data integrity is maintained by making certain that collected data is relevant for the purposes for which it is used, and that it is accurate, complete and current;
  * Access to their personal information is given to individuals so they may correct, amend, or delete information where it is inaccurate; and  

  * Enforcement of the Safe Harbor Principles is carried out.
